Digi-dream lights up the screen; numbers rise; the future gleams.
Pitch deck loaded, ready to ignite; vision sharp as neon in the night.
Investors watching, hearts sync to the code, turning data into rocket-fuel mode.
All our dreams in one slide; growth charts on the rise; we're the spark they can't deny.
We are the code that lights the night, bold and electric, taking flight.
From garage startups to sky-high streams; retro-electro fueling our dreams.
Milestones stacking like digital bricks; ROI rhythms making them tick.
Plug into our network; watch us thrive, building tomorrow, alive with drive.
Count pre-orders; feel the servers hum; this is how revolutions come.
We are the code that lights the night, bold and electric, taking flight.
From garage startups to sky-high streams; retro-electro fueling our dreams.